<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<translations>
    <translation id="homeLng">
        <En>Home</En>
        <Es>Inicio</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="bookingLng">
        <En>Booking</En>
        <Es>Reserve</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="aboutLng">
        <En>About</En>
        <Es>Nosotros</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="contactLng">
        <En>Contact</En>
        <Es>Contacto</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="contactLng">
        <En>Contact</En>
        <Es>Contacto</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="bookNowLng">
        <En>Book Now</En>
        <Es>Reserve</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="welcomeLng">
        <En>Welcome</En>
        <Es>Bienvenido</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="toLng">
        <En>to Hotel Villa Tournon</En>
        <Es>a Hotel Villa Tournon</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="readMoreLng">
        <En>Read more</En>
        <Es>Leer más</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="servicesLng">
        <En>Services</En>
        <Es>Servicios</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="offerLng">
        <En>We offer</En>
        <Es>Ofrecemos</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ebonyLng">
        <En>Ebony and Ivory Restaurant</En>
        <Es>Restaurante Ebony and Ivory</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="rinconAzulLng">
        <En>Rincón Azul Restaurant</En>
        <Es>Restaurante Rincón Azul</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="poolLng">
        <En>Pool and Jacuzzi</En>
        <Es>Piscina y Jacuzzi</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="businessLng">
        <En>Business Center</En>
        <Es>Salas de negocios</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="specialActivitiesLng">
        <En>Events Hall</En>
        <Es>Actividades especiales</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="artLng">
        <En>Art Gallery</En>
        <Es>Galería de Arte</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="hotelMinLng">
        <En>Hotel Villa Tournon has 80 rooms including standard, Superior and De Luxe rooms. Some of the rooms stand out for their view to a garden surrounding the pool and Jacuzzi; In addition to a beautiful view of San Jose at night, with its illuminated buildings, embedded in a Hill as competing with each other to exceed in height.</En>
        <Es>Hotel Villa Tournon tiene 80 habitaciones entre Estándar, Superior y De Luxe. Algunas de la habitaciones se destacan por su vista hacia un amplio jardín rodeando la piscina y jacuzzi; además de una hermosa vista de San José especialmente de noche, con sus edificios iluminados, incrustados en una loma como compitiendo entre ellos para superar en altura.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="roomsLng">
        <En>Rooms</En>
        <Es>Habitaciones</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="standardLng">
        <En>The rooms have a fine wood park flooring, they were the first hotel rooms when it was permitted the use and marketing of this protected wood currently by law.</En>
        <Es>Todas las habitaciones son de pisos de fina madera parqué, fueron las primeras habitaciones del hotel cuando era permitido el uso y comercialización de esta protegida madera en la actualidad por ley.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="superiorLng">
        <En>They have a spacious bathroom with shower and tub and its respective amenities, an area with living room, some with King size bed and other with two double beds.</En>
        <Es>Disponen de amplio baño con ducha y tina y sus respectivos amenidades, un área con sala de estar, algunas con cama King y otras con dos camas matrimoniales.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="deluxeLng">
        <En>Are distinguished by its exquisite location, overlooking a fountain, surrounded by a garden in a courtyard which ensures peace of mind.</En>
        <Es>Se distinguen por su exquisita ubicación, vista hacia una fuente, rodeado por un jardín en un patio interno que garantiza tranquilidad.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="followLng">
        <En>Follow us</En>
        <Es>Síganos</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="footerLng">
        <En>Hotel Villa Tournon always serves you in a style reserved to serve the most demanding guest.</En>
        <Es>Hotel Villa Tournon siempre sirve con estilo a los huéspedes más exigentes.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="roomsDescLng">
        <En>Some of the rooms stand out for their views of a large garden surrounding the pool and Jacuzzi; In addition to the beautiful one of San Jose at night with its illuminated buildings, embedded in a Hill as competing with each other to exceed in height.</En>
        <Es>Algunas de las habitaciones se destacan por su vista hacia un amplio jardín rodeando la piscina y  jacuzzi; además de una hermosa vista de San José, de noche con sus edificios iluminados, incrustados en una loma como compitiendo entre ellos para superar en altura.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="priceLng">
        <En>Price</En>
        <Es>Precio</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="hotelLng">
        <En>This is a hotel of 80 rooms including standard, Superior and De Luxe rooms. Some of the rooms stand out for their view to a garden surrounding the pool and Jacuzzi; In addition to a beautiful view of San Jose at night, with its illuminated buildings, embedded in a Hill as competing with each other to exceed in height. Hotel Villas Tournon is situated in the exclusive executive area of Barrio Tournon, just eight blocks from the central avenue of San Jose; the capital of Costa Rica. A few steps away are located: relevant institutions of the State, a major private university, shopping malls, Executive centres, transport terminal that goes to the Caribbean coast of Costa Rica, Simón Bolívar park, and a butterfly garden. The hotel was built at the beginning of the 1980s on a split level ground having a terrace formation. It consists of three floors. You enter the third floor and go down to the second and then to the first. Continuing the descent you will reach the swimming pool and Jacuzzi area surrounded by a beautiful and colorful garden. In the architectural structure of this building you will appreciate a stunning sky craft, made with fine and precious wood in the Lobby, Bar and the restaurant Rincon Azul. Also the floors of most of the rooms are furnished with the mention material, already prohibited the felling and sale by law in our country. All areas of the Villa Tournon Hotel are decorated with many paintings of different themes and techniques by Costa Rican and foreign authors; which make this hotel an authentic Gallery. Art and culture are its emblem. The Congregation of these works of art, together with the friendly service of the staff is an invitation to learn more about Costa Rica.</En>
        <Es>Se trata de un hotel de 80 habitaciones entre habitaciones Estándar, Superior y De Luxe. Algunas de la habitaciones se destacan por su vista hacia un amplio jardín rodeando la piscina y jacuzzi; además de una hermosa vista de San José de noche, con sus edificios iluminados, incrustados en una loma como compitiendo entre ellos para superar en altura. Hotel Villas Tournon está ubicado en la exclusiva área ejecutiva de Barrio Tournon, a solo ocho cuadras de la avenida central de San José; la capital de Costa Rica. A escasos pasos se ubica una importante universidad privada, instituciones relevantes del estado, centros comerciales, centros ejecutivos, terminal de transporte hacia la zona del Caribe, el parque Simón Bolívar, jardín de mariposas. El hotel fue construido a principio de los años 80 sobre un terreno irregular en terraza; consta de tres pisos. Se ingresa por el tercer piso para trasladarse a la segunda y la primera planta. Continuando el descenso se llega al área de la piscina y jacuzzi rodeado de un hermoso y colorido jardín. Se aprecia en la arquitectónica del edificio un impresionante cielo artesanado, de fina y preciada madera en las áreas del Lobby, Bar y Restaurante Rincón Azul. Así mismo los pisos de la mayoría de las habitaciones son de la citada madera, ya prohibido su tala y venta por ley en nuestro país. Todas las áreas del Hotel Villa Tournon están engalanadas con pinturas de diferentes temáticas y técnicas, de autores costarricenses y extranjeros; los cuales convierten este hotel en una auténtica Galería. El arte y la cultura son su emblema. La congregación de estas obras de arte acompañado del amable servicio del personal es una invitación para conocer más de Costa Rica.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="pricesFromLng">
        <En>Prices from</En>
        <Es>Precios desde</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="checkInCheckOutLng">
        <En>Check-In: 15:00 - Check-Out: 12:00</En>
        <Es>Entrada: 15:00 - Salida: 12:00</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="placesVisitLng">
        <En>Places you can visit in walking distance:</En>
        <Es>Lugares que puede recorrer caminando:</Es>
    </translation>
</translations>