<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<translations>
    <translation id="homeLng">
        <En>Home</En>
        <Es>Inicio</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="bookingLng">
        <En>Booking</En>
        <Es>Reserve</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="aboutLng">
        <En>About</En>
        <Es>Nosotros</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="contactLng">
        <En>Contact</En>
        <Es>Contacto</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="contactLng">
        <En>Contact</En>
        <Es>Contacto</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="bookNowLng">
        <En>Book Now</En>
        <Es>Reserve</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="welcomeLng">
        <En>Welcome</En>
        <Es>Bienvenido</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="toLng">
        <En>to Hotel Villa Tournon</En>
        <Es>a Hotel Villa Tournon</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="readMoreLng">
        <En>Read more</En>
        <Es>Leer más</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="servicesLng">
        <En>Services</En>
        <Es>Servicios</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="offerLng">
        <En>We offer</En>
        <Es>Ofrecemos</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ebonyLng">
        <En>Ebony and Ivory Restaurant</En>
        <Es>Restaurante Ebony and Ivory</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="rinconAzulLng">
        <En>Rincón Azul Restaurant</En>
        <Es>Restaurante Rincón Azul</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="poolLng">
        <En>Pool and Jacuzzi</En>
        <Es>Piscina y Jacuzzi</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="businessLng">
        <En>Business Center</En>
        <Es>Salas de negocios</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="specialActivitiesLng">
        <En>Events Hall</En>
        <Es>Actividades especiales</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="artLng">
        <En>Art Gallery</En>
        <Es>Galería de Arte</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="photoGalleryLng">
        <En>Photo Gallery</En>
        <Es>Galería de Fotos</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="hotelMinLng">
        <En>Hotel Villa Tournon has 80 rooms including standard, Superior and De Luxe rooms. Some of the rooms stand out for their view to a garden surrounding the pool and Jacuzzi; In addition to a beautiful view of San Jose at night, with its illuminated buildings, embedded in a Hill as competing with each other to exceed in height.</En>
        <Es>Hotel Villa Tournon tiene 80 habitaciones entre Estándar, Superior y De Luxe. Algunas de la habitaciones se destacan por su vista hacia un amplio jardín rodeando la piscina y jacuzzi; además de una hermosa vista de San José especialmente de noche, con sus edificios iluminados, incrustados en una loma como compitiendo entre ellos para superar en altura.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="roomsLng">
        <En>Rooms</En>
        <Es>Habitaciones</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="standardLng">
        <En>The rooms have a fine wood park flooring, they were the first hotel rooms when it was permitted the use and marketing of this protected wood currently by law.</En>
        <Es>Todas las habitaciones son de pisos de fina madera parqué, fueron las primeras habitaciones del hotel cuando era permitido el uso y comercialización de esta protegida madera en la actualidad por ley.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="superiorLng">
        <En>They have a spacious bathroom with shower and tub and its respective amenities, an area with living room, some with King size bed and other with two double beds.</En>
        <Es>Disponen de amplio baño con ducha y tina y sus respectivos amenidades, un área con sala de estar, algunas con cama King y otras con dos camas matrimoniales.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="deluxeLng">
        <En>Are distinguished by its exquisite location, overlooking a fountain, surrounded by a garden in a courtyard which ensures peace of mind.</En>
        <Es>Se distinguen por su exquisita ubicación, vista hacia una fuente, rodeado por un jardín en un patio interno que garantiza tranquilidad.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="followLng">
        <En>Follow us</En>
        <Es>Síganos</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="footerLng">
        <En>Hotel Villa Tournon always serves you in a style reserved to serve the most demanding guest.</En>
        <Es>Hotel Villa Tournon siempre sirve con estilo a los huéspedes más exigentes.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="roomsDescLng">
        <En>Some of the rooms stand out for their views of a large garden surrounding the pool and Jacuzzi; In addition to the beautiful one of San Jose at night with its illuminated buildings, embedded in a Hill as competing with each other to exceed in height.</En>
        <Es>Algunas de las habitaciones se destacan por su vista hacia un amplio jardín rodeando la piscina y  jacuzzi; además de una hermosa vista de San José, de noche con sus edificios iluminados, incrustados en una loma como compitiendo entre ellos para superar en altura.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="priceLng">
        <En>Price</En>
        <Es>Precio</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="hotelLng">
        <En>This is a hotel of 80 rooms including standard, Superior and De Luxe rooms. Some of the rooms stand out for their view to a garden surrounding the pool and Jacuzzi; In addition to a beautiful view of San Jose at night, with its illuminated buildings, embedded in a Hill as competing with each other to exceed in height. Hotel Villas Tournon is situated in the exclusive executive area of Barrio Tournon, just eight blocks from the central avenue of San Jose; the capital of Costa Rica. A few steps away are located: relevant institutions of the State, a major private university, shopping malls, Executive centres, transport terminal that goes to the Caribbean coast of Costa Rica, Simón Bolívar park, and a butterfly garden. The hotel was built at the beginning of the 1980s on a split level ground having a terrace formation. It consists of three floors. You enter the third floor and go down to the second and then to the first. Continuing the descent you will reach the swimming pool and Jacuzzi area surrounded by a beautiful and colorful garden. In the architectural structure of this building you will appreciate a stunning sky craft, made with fine and precious wood in the Lobby, Bar and the restaurant Rincon Azul. Also the floors of most of the rooms are furnished with the mention material, already prohibited the felling and sale by law in our country. All areas of the Villa Tournon Hotel are decorated with many paintings of different themes and techniques by Costa Rican and foreign authors; which make this hotel an authentic Gallery. Art and culture are its emblem. The Congregation of these works of art, together with the friendly service of the staff is an invitation to learn more about Costa Rica.</En>
        <Es>Hotel Villa Tournon tiene 80 habitaciones entre Estándar, Superior y De Luxe. Algunas de la habitaciones se destacan por su vista hacia un amplio jardín rodeando la piscina y jacuzzi; además de una hermosa vista de San José especialmente de noche, con sus edificios iluminados, incrustados en una loma como compitiendo entre ellos para superar en altura. Está situado en la exclusiva área ejecutiva de Barrio Tournon, a solo ocho cuadras de la avenida central de San José; la capital de Costa Rica. A escasos pasos se ubica una importante universidad privada, instituciones relevantes del estado, centros comerciales, centros ejecutivos, terminal de transporte hacia la zona del Caribe, el Parque Simón Bolívar, Jardín de mariposas y otros lugares de interés. El hotel, construido a principio de los años 80 sobre un terreno irregular en terraza; consta de tres pisos. Se ingresa por el tercer piso para trasladarse a la segunda y la primera planta. Continuando el descenso se llega al área de la piscina y jacuzzi rodeado de un hermoso y colorido jardín. Se aprecia en la arquitectónica del edificio un impresionante cielo artesanado, de fina y preciada madera en las áreas del Lobby, Bar y Restaurante Rincón Azul. Así mismo los pisos de la mayoría de las habitaciones son de la citada madera, ya prohibido su tala y venta por ley en nuestro país. Todas las áreas del Hotel están engalanadas con pinturas de diferentes temáticas y técnicas, de autores costarricenses y extranjeros; los cuales convierten este hotel en una auténtica Galería. El arte y la cultura son su emblema. La congregación de estas obras de arte acompañado del amable servicio del personal es una invitación para conocer más de Costa Rica.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="pricesFromLng">
        <En>Prices from</En>
        <Es>Precios desde</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="checkInCheckOutLng">
        <En>Check-In: 15:00 - Check-Out: 12:00</En>
        <Es>Entrada: 15:00 - Salida: 12:00</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="placesVisitLng">
        <En>Places you can visit in walking distance:</En>
        <Es>Lugares que puede recorrer caminando:</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ebonyDescLng">
        <En>Ebony and Ivory restaurant is a space recently designed in the hotel consisting of a modern and warm environment; where you can distinguish the decoration in black and white, in the ceilings, walls, furniture and tableware; additionally supplemented with arts including paintings, photographs and sculptures. The cuisine also shares this dichotomy. You will be able to enjoy a dish fusion regarding European food mainly Spanish, French, and Italian likewise in one sense, and on the other, the cuisine of the Caribbean countries. The Caribbean representing the concept of Ebony and the european of Ivory.</En>
        <Es>El Restaurante Ebony and Ivory es un espacio recientemente diseñado en el hotel que consta de un entorno moderno y cálido; en la que se evidencia una decoración en blanco y negro, entre cielos, paredes, muebles y menaje; además complementado con artes entre pinturas, fotografías y esculturas. Su gastronomía comparte también esta dicotomía. La cocina es una fusión de platos europeos, fundamentalmente de las cocinas española, italiana y francesa, por una parte, por la otra, la culinaria de los países caribeños. La Caribeña en representación del concepto de Ebony y la europea a Ivory.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="rinconAzulDescLng">
        <En>This dining area is decorated with embossed art work, tapestries with scenes recreating historic moments of the harvest of coffee in our country; watercolor paintings, oil paintings, beautiful stained glass windows and a brick fireplace are just some of the objects that you can admire and observe while you relish our national and international gastronomic specialties in which prevails the tender care and the notorious courtesy of the staff. This attention to guests is extended from 6 am until 10 pm. Social events can be held in this area and it has a capacity for 150 people.</En>
        <Es>La decoración y ambientación en el restaurante se sirve en este espacio para que genere placer. En él nos esforzamos en personalizar y gratificar con nuestros servicios su estadía, crear memorables momentos que llegan más allá de sus expectativas. El comedor está decorado con artes de obra en repujados, tapices con escenas que recrea momentos históricos de la cosecha de café en nuestro país; pinturas en acuarela y en oleo; hermosos vitrales y una chimenea en ladrillos son algunos de los objetos que se pueden admirar y observar mientras se disgustan de nuestros especialidades gastronómicas nacionales e internacional, en donde prevalece la amabilidad y la notoria cortesía del personal. Esta atención a los huéspedes se prolonga desde las 6 am hasta las 10 pm.En esta área se celebran todo tipo de eventos sociales y tiene una capacidad para 150 personas.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="businessCenterDescLng">
        <En>The business center has a capacity of up to 6 people, to organize business meetings, breakfast, presentations and video conferences, among others. Upon request, we provide for renting Video Beam.</En>
        <Es>El centro de negocios tiene una capacidad de hasta 6 personas, para organizar encuentros de trabajo, desayuno, presentaciones y video de conferencias, entre otros. A requerimiento, ofrecemos en alquiler Video Beam.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="eventsHallDescLng">
        <En>The hotel offers the possibility of holding various events with a differentiated service where premium attitude is displayed. There are two rooms enabled “La Jungla” and “Rincón Azul” with capacity of 45 and 150 people respectively, are enabled and equipped with materials and equipment needs, suitable for events such as conferences, seminars, weddings, baby showers, graduation party, lunches and private dinners; Likewise, enjoy our services of coffee break and the range of cuisine that we offer you in format menu, buffet or cocktail.</En>
        <Es>El hotel ofrece la posibilidad de celebrar distintos eventos con un servicio diferenciado donde prima la actitud. Hay dos salas habilitadas “La Jungla” y “Rincón Azul” con capacidad de 45 y 150 personas respectivamente, están habilitadas y equipadas con materiales y equipos idóneos a las necesidades, para eventos como conferencias, bodas, seminarios, baby showers, fiesta de graduación, almuerzos y cenas privadas; así mismo, disfruta de nuestros servicios de coffe break y la gama de gastronomía que le ofrecemos en formato de menú, buffet o coctel.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="artGalleryDescLng">
        <En>Hotel Villa Tournon serves as an art gallery. In the areas of the hotel you will be encountering with an exposition of the three main historical traditional fine arts: architecture, sculpture and painting most of all.</En>
        <Es>Hotel Villa Tournon es una galería de arte. En las diferentes áreas del hotel se aprecia una exposición de tres de las bellas artes históricamente tradicionales: la arquitectura, la escultura y la pintura. Siendo esta la más fecunda en el hotel.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="poolJacuzziDescLng">
        <En>The area of garden where the swimming pool and Jacuzzi are, is a unique full world retreat accuses a perfect harmony of sun and shade, where some times the grove green are interrupted by the Sun causing shadow and other moment the sun positioned at another point which avoids disruption of trees in its path.</En>
        <Es>El área de jardín donde se encuentra la piscina y jacuzzi, es un refugio único en pleno orbe, acusa una perfección armoniosa entre sol y sombra, en que unas veces el verdor de la arboleda interrumpe el sol causando sombra y en otros momentos, el sol se posiciona en otro punto donde evade la interrupción de los arboles en su trayectoria.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="viewFullGalleryLng">
        <En>View Full Gallery</En>
        <Es>Ver todas las fotos</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="phtotoGalleryLng">
        <En>Photo Gallery</En>
        <Es>Galería de fotos</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ebonyLeft1Lng">
        <En>EUROPEAN FUSION CUISINE</En>
        <Es>FUSIÓN DE GASTRONOMÍA EUROPEA</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ebonyLeft2Lng">
        <En>and CARIBBEAN DELIGHTS</En>
        <Es>Y DELICIAS CARIBEÑAS</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ebonyRight1Lng">
        <En>FOR YOUR HEALTH</En>
        <Es>PARA SU SALUD</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ebonyRight2Lng">
        <En>VEGGIE FOOD</En>
        <Es>ALIMENTOS VEGGIE</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ebonyDesc1Lng">
        <En>Ebony and Ivory restaurant is a space recently designed in the hotel consisting of a modern and warm environment; where you can distinguish the decoration in black and white, in the ceilings, walls, furniture and tableware; additionally supplemented with arts including paintings, photographs and sculptures.</En>
        <Es>El Restaurante Ebony and Ivory es un espacio recientemente diseñado en el hotel que consta de un entorno moderno y cálido; en la que se evidencia una decoración en blanco y negro, entre cielos, paredes, muebles y menaje; además complementado con artes entre pinturas, fotografías y esculturas.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ebonyDesc2Lng">
        <En>The cuisine also shares this dichotomy. You will be able to enjoy a dish fusion regarding European food mainly Spanish, French, and Italian likewise in one sense, and on the other, the cuisine of the Caribbean countries. The Caribbean representing the concept of Ebony and the european of Ivory.</En>
        <Es>Su gastronomía comparte también esta dicotomía. La cocina es una fusión de platos europeos, fundamentalmente de las cocinas española, italiana y francesa, por una parte, por la otra, la culinaria de los países caribeños. La Caribeña en representación del concepto de Ebony y la europea a Ivory.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="privaterDiningLng">
        <En>Private dining</En>
        <Es>Ambiente privado</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="fromCelebrationsLng">
        <En>From celebrations to intimate gatherings</En>
        <Es>Desde celebraciones a reuniones íntimas</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="doingBusinessLng">
        <En>Doing Business</En>
        <Es>Haga Negocios</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="doingBusinessDescLng">
        <En>Thematic restaurant oriented to business men and women who want to take lunch or dinner time to contact with business people and establish commercial relations.</En>
        <Es>Restaurante temático orientado a hombres y mujeres de negocios que desean aprovechar la hora de almuerzo o cena para citas de negocios o establecer relaciones comerciales.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="gourmetLng">
        <En>Gourmet Restaurant</En>
        <Es>Restaurante Gourmet</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="gourmetDescLng">
        <En>High-quality restaurant with gourmet dishes, upscale decoration and a qualified service at its best.</En>
        <Es>Restaurante de alto nivel, con platos gourmet e innovadora decoración; además de un servicio súper calificado.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="perfectArmonyLng">
        <En>Perfect Armony</En>
        <Es>Perfecta Armonía</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="perfectArmonyDescLng">
        <En>A space for two where the sensorialty of the restaurant will seduces you to a perfect harmony.</En>
        <Es>Un espacio para los dos donde la sensorialidad del restaurante le seduce en una perfecta armonía.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ArtGalleyDesc1Lng">
        <En>Hotel Villa Tournon serves as an art gallery. In the areas of the hotel you will be encountering with an exposition of the three main historical traditional fine arts: architecture, sculpture and painting most of all.</En>
        <Es>Hotel Villa Tournon es una galería de arte. En las diferentes áreas del hotel se aprecia una exposición de tres de las bellas artes históricamente tradicionales: la arquitectura, la escultura y la pintura. Siendo esta la más fecunda en el hotel.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ArtGalleyDesc2Lng">
        <En>A specify appreciation of architecture art can be seen in the sky craft, in the areas of the lobby, restaurant and bar.</En>
        <Es>Una específica apreciación de arte arquitectónico es el artesanado que se puede observar en los cielos de las áreas del lobby, restaurante y bar.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ArtGalleyDesc3Lng">
        <En>Two sculpture pieces; one, a synonym of the lower body up to the waist of a woman, with a metamorphosis extension upward, in proportion in size to the related lower body. This piece was sculptured from a Guanacaste wood which is the national tree of Costa Rica; another is a sensory contemplation that can be held observing an African piece made out of Ebony wood. This work represents an African queen tenderly embracing two small children standing at her side. Rooms, passages and other areas are submitted to dozen of painting that make Hotel Villa Tournon a perfect gallery. This beauty is a key component to the experience added to your stay away from home</En>
        <Es>Así mismo, se pueden subrayar dos piezas de escultura: uno, un sinónimo de la parte inferior de una mujer desde la cintura hacia abajo, con una extensión de metamorfosis hacia arriba, en proporción al tamaño de la parte inferior del cuerpo relacionado. Esta pieza fue esculpida en madera de Guanacaste, que es el árbol nacional de Costa Rica; la otra obra es una pieza africana, tallada en madera de ébano. Este trabajo representa a una reina africana abrazando tiernamente dos niños pequeños de pie a su lado. Las habitaciones, pasillos y otras áreas están sometidas a docenas de pinturas que hacen del Hotel Villa Tournon una extraordinaria galería. Esta belleza es un componente clave para la experiencia añadida a su estancia fuera de casa.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ArtGalleyDesc4Lng">
        <En>We welcome you to enjoy the variety of these visual arts.</En>
        <Es>Le invitamos a disfrutar de la variedad de estas artes visuales.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="ContactUsLng">
        <En>Contact Us</En>
        <Es>Contáctenos</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="DropLineLng">
        <En>Drop us a line</En>
        <Es>Escríbanos con confianza, estamos para servir</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="WriteLng">
        <En>Write</En>
        <Es>Escriba</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="checkInCheckOutEspLng">
        <En>Check-In: 15:00 - Check-Out: 12:00 *</En>
        <Es>Entrada: 15:00 - Salida: 12:00 *</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="changeSchedLng">
        <En>*Late check-out could be possible upon availability</En>
        <Es>*La salida podría ser más tarde dependiendo de la disponibilidad</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="aboutUsLng">
        <En>About Us</En>
        <Es>Acerca de Nosotros</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="aboutUsDesc1Lng">
        <En>I am Leslie Wilson Shimpson, General Manager of Hotel Villa Tournon, Costa Rican by birth. I started working in hospitality at the age of 21 in 1966 as a waiter.</En>
        <Es>Soy Leslie Wilson Shimpson, Gerente General del Hotel Villa Tournon, Costarricense de nacimiento. Comencé a trabajar en hotelería a la edad de 21 años en 1966, como camarero.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="aboutUsDesc2Lng">
        <En>Job opportunities in Costa Rica was not easy then; Therefore I began to offer my services to work for free with the firm conviction that in time, the workplace would offer to pay me a salary; but the places I visited; I guess they had doubt my good faith.</En>
        <Es>lugar de trabajo me ofrecería pagar un salario; mas los lugares que visité; supongo que tuvieron duda de mi buena fe.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="aboutUsDesc3Lng">
        <En>In less than two years working as a waiter and in other post I got to the position of assistant manager of the hotel; months before completing four years of work in the company, my boss and I become partners in a new hotel. After two years I acquired if share and became the sole owner. During that period I had not completed high school.</En>
        <Es>En menos de dos años trabajando como camarero y en otros puestos me escale al puesto de asistente del Gerente del hotel; meses antes de completar cuatro años de trabajar en la empresa, mi jefe y yo nos convertimos en socios en un nuevo hotel. Transcurridos dos años adquirí su participación y me convertí en el único propietario. Durante ese período no había completado la escuela secundaria.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="aboutUsDesc4Lng">
        <En>Today I am a lawyer and also went to journalism school.</En>
        <Es>En la actualidad soy abogado y también fui a la escuela de periodismo.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="aboutUsDesc5Lng">
        <En>Hotel Villa Tournon I founded in 1992. Forty-nine years have passed since I start working in hospitality. I have a great passion for my job, I love dealing with people of all nationalities. My mission is to convey to a new generation of hospitality workers the satisfaction which can be experienced assisting strangers every day.</En>
        <Es>Fundé Hotel Villa Tournon en 1992.Cuarenta y nueve años han transcurrido desde que empecé a trabajar en hotelería. Tengo una gran pasión por mi trabajo, me encanta tratar con la gente de todas las nacionalidades. Mi misión es transmitir a una nueva generación en hospitalidad la satisfacción que se experimenta apoyando a extraños todos los días.</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="aboutUsDesc6Lng">
        <En>Thanks for your visit; I hope you enjoy our web site</En>
        <Es>Gracias por visitar nuestra página, espero que la disfruten</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="bookinInfoLng">
        <En>Booking Info</En>
        <Es>Información de la reserva</Es>
    </translation>
    <translation id="personalInfoLng">
        <En>Personal Info</En>
        <Es>Información Personal</Es>
    </translation>
</translations>